("Closer" by The Chainsmokers ft. Halsey)
♪ Hey I was doing just
fine before I met you ♪
♪ I drink too much and that's an issue ♪
♪ But I'm okay ♪
♪ Hey you tell your friends
it was nice to meet them ♪
♪ But I hope I never see them again ♪
♪ I know it breaks your heart ♪
♪ Moved to the city in a broke-down car ♪
♪ And four years no calls ♪
♪ Now you're looking
pretty in a hotel bar ♪
♪ And I I I I I can't stop ♪
♪ No I I I I I can't stop ♪
♪ So baby pull me closer ♪
♪ In the back seat of your Rover ♪
♪ That I know you can't afford ♪
♪ Bite that tattoo on your shoulder ♪
♪ Pull the sheets right off the corner ♪
♪ Of that mattress that you stole ♪
♪ From your roommate back in Boulder ♪
♪ We ain't ever getting older ♪
♪ You look as good as the day I met you ♪
♪ I forget just why I left you ♪
♪ I was insane ♪
♪ Stay and play that Blink-182 song ♪
♪ That we beat to death in Tucson ♪
♪ Okay ♪
♪ I know it breaks your heart ♪
♪ Moved to the city in a broke-down car ♪
♪ And four years no call ♪
♪ Now I'm looking pretty in a hotel bar ♪
♪ And I I I I I can't stop ♪
♪ No I I I I I can't stop ♪
♪ So baby pull me closer ♪
♪ In the back seat of your Rover ♪
♪ That I know you can't afford ♪
♪ Bite that tattoo on your shoulder ♪
♪ Pull the sheets right off the corner ♪
♪ Of that mattress that you stole ♪
♪ From your roommate back in Boulder ♪
♪ We ain't ever getting older ♪
♪ So baby pull me closer ♪
♪ In the back seat of your Rover ♪
♪ That I know you can't afford ♪
♪ Bite that tattoo on your shoulder ♪
♪ Pull the sheets right off the corner ♪
♪ Of that mattress that you stole ♪
♪ From your roommate back in Boulder ♪
♪ We ain't ever getting older ♪
♪ No we ain't ever getting older ♪